A Finding Aid to the Fletcher Benton Papers, 1934-2014, in the Archives of American Art AAA.bentflet
Archives of American Art
Fletcher Benton papers
1934-2014
AAA.bentflet
Archives of American Art
7.9 Linear feet
The papers of sculptor and painter Fletcher Benton measure 7.9 linear feet and date from 1934 to 2014. They document his career as a sculptor with international presence through certificates, personal photographs, legal papers, correspondence, exhibition and commission documentation, clippings, exhibition-related printed materials, broadcast materials, publications about his work, an editioned kinetic Christmas card, and photographs, sound and video recordings, and motion picture film documenting his work and career.
Benton, Fletcher
Arrangement note
This collection is arranged as nine series.
Series 1: Biographical Material (0.3 linear feet; boxes 1, 9)
Series 2: Correspondence (1 linear foot; boxes 1, 2, OV 10)
Series 3: Interviews (0.3 linear feet; box 2)
Series 4: Exhibition and Commission Files (1.9 linear feet; boxes 2-4, OV 11-13, RD 14)
Series 5: Printed Materials (2.3 linear feet; boxes 4-6, OV 10)
Series 6: Broadcast Materials (1.1 linear foot; boxes 6-7)
Series 7: Photographic and Moving Image Matarials (0.3 linear feet; boxes 7, 9)
Series 8: Artwork (1 item; box 7)
Series 9: An American Artist Video Recordings (0.6 linear feet; boxes 7-8)
Related Archival Materials note
Also found in the Archives of American Art is an oral history interview with Fletcher Benton conducted by Paul J. Karlstrom, 1989 May 2-4 is available on the Archives of American Art website.
Immediate Source of Acquisition note
Donated 2005-2006 and 2014 by Fletcher Benton. Benton's wife, Bobbie Benton, organized the material by subject matter and date.
Conditions Governing Access note
Use of original papers requires an appointment. Use of audiovisual material without a duplicate copy requires advanced notice.
Biographical/Historical note
Fletcher Benton was born in Jackson, Ohio in 1931 to Fletcher and Nell Cavett Benton and was the oldest of three children. Benton graduated from Jackson High School in 1949. After serving in the Navy he graduated from Miami University (Oxford, Ohio) in 1956 and moved to San Francisco, where he started working as an instructor at the California College of Arts and Crafts in 1959. He was in San Francisco during the flourishing of the Beat generation, where he had a studio in the North beach area and exhibited at coffee house galleries.
After travelling around Europe in 1960, Benton moved to New York City where he tried to make his living through painting and teaching privately. During those years he was supported by Jackson’s local arts patron and family friend, Lillian E. Jones. In 1960 he had his first solo exhibition at Gump’s gallery in San Francisco, but his work was taken down after one day because it was considered obscene for including female nudes. He returned to San Francisco in late 1961.
In 1966 Fletcher started teaching at the San Francisco Art Institute and established himself as a primary figure of American kinetic art. In 1966, Peter Selz included his work in the exhibition Directions in Kinetic Sculpture at the University Art Gallery in Berkeley, CA. During the exhibition Benton met the artists Pol Bury and George Rickey with whom he became friends. The exhibition, along with an article "The Movement Movement" that appeared in Time magazine the same year, established Benton's reputation as a significant American Kinetic artist. He also started teaching at the California State University in San José in 1967 where he continued working until 1986.
By 1974 Benton abandoned kinetic art to continue exploring sculpture in three dimensions in a style that became known as "new constructivism." The artworks were conceived in the series Folded Circles and Folded Square Alphabets and were produced in bronze, aluminum and steel. It was also during the 1970s that he started doing large-scale commissions such as the 1977 IBM commission.
Between 1981 and 1984 Benton constructed his studio in Dore Street in the Market district of San Francisco where he continues to work today. During the 1980s Benton started his Balanced/Unbalanced series, which introduced the idea of gravity using geometric forms in different formats and sizes.
From 1984 he began to show more work in Europe, especially in Germany, where in 1993 he got a major commission to create a colossal public sculpture in Cologne entitled Steel Watercolor Triangle Ring. It was also in Germany where Benton encountered the work of Wassily Kandinsky and Kazimir Malevich, and he began work on his Construct Relief series in reponse, which he dedicated to Kandinsky. These geometric constructions are flat, canvas-like steel structures that combine features of painting and sculpture. As the series evolved, the work became more like painting, constructed to hang on the wall without a back piece, so they seem to be floating in the space.
Benton continues to live and work in San Francisco and is represented by multiple galleries in the United States and Germany.
Scope and Contents note
The papers of sculptor and painter Fletcher Benton measure 7.9 linear feet and date from 1934 to 2014. They document his career through personal photographs, legal papers, correspondence, exhibition and commission documentation, clippings, exhibition-related printed materials, broadcast materials, publications about his work, an editioned kinetic Christmas card, photographs, sound and video recordings, and motion picture film.
Biographical Materials include personal photographs, legal documents related to a court case with book designer Ed Marquand, biographical texts, interview transcripts, and a home video made by the artist. Correspondence is with other artists, friends, galleries, museums and other institutions, including George W. Neubert, André Emmerich Gallery, Pieter Sanders, Pol Bury, George Rickey, Ulfert Wilke, Marlene Louchheim, DeWain Valentine, Lillian E. Jones, and Edward Lucie-Smith. Interviews include sound recordings of interviews with Benton by academics and journalists, including Edward Lucie-Smith, Dan Tooker, and Dan De Wilde.
Exhibition and Commission Files consist of correspondence with galleries, museums and commission patrons; financial records; shipping and subcontracting documentation; motion picture film, video, and sound recordings related to exhibitions and installations; and planning and design materials. Series includes a significant amount of oversized drawings and plans for site-specific work. There is a large volume documentation from the Folded Circle-Arc commission by Stanley Consultants, Inc. in Muscatine, Iowa; the California/International Arts Foundation Traveling Sculpture Exhibition; Double Folded Circle Ring in Brussels and Double Circle Folded by Cedars Sinai Medical Center in Los Angeles.
Printed Materials include news clippings related to Benton’s career, as well as brochures, exhibition catalogs, posters and other printed materials related to exhibitions and commissions. Broadcast materials include television news footage, radio and television interviews, documentaries, and promotional materials made by galleries and other cultural institutions.
Photographic and Moving Image Materials include art-related images showing Benton in his studio and images of exhibitions, installations and inaugurations. Also found are still photographs and motion picture films of artworks, including paintings, sculptures, and kinetic drawings, and a series of photographs of sculptures taken by David Finn.
Artwork consists of an editioned art Christmas card created by Benton for Galeria Bonino in New York from 1969. An American Artist Moving Image Materials consist of 13 videocassettes (VHS) which document the production process of the documentary Fletcher Benton: An American Artist by Morgan Cavett. There is footage from interviews with Benton and with curator George W. Neubert, footage of San Francisco with comments from Benton about his time there, interviews with the artist’s studio assistants, images of his studio in Dore street and a couple of almost finished rough versions of the documentary.
André Emmerich Gallery; Bury, Pol, 1922-2005; De Wilde, Dan; Finn, David; Galerie Denino.; Jones, Lillian E.; Louchheim, Marlene; Lucie-Smith, Edward; Marquand, Ed; Neubert, George W.; Rickey, George; Sanders, Pieter; Tooker, Dan; Valentine, De Wain, 1936-; Wilke, Ulfert, 1907-1987; Artists' studios--Photographs; Christmas cards; Drawings; Interviews; Motion pictures (visual works); Painters--California--San Francisco; Photographs; Sculptors--California--San Francisco; Sound recordings; Transcripts; Video recordings
- Biographical Materials, 1934-2013; Series 1; 0.3 Linear feet Box 1 and 9
  Arrangement note
  Photographs and moving images of Benton working in his studio, of his artwork, and art-related events are found in series 7, Photographic and Moving Image Materials. Additional photographs and moving images related to exhibitions and commissions are found in series 4, Exhibitions and Commission files.
  Scope and Contents note
  Biographical material includes four folders of photographs from Benton's childhood to the present and a number of personal photographs of the artist with family members and art personalities including Harold Paris, Edward Lucie-Smith, Dewain Valentine and Peter Selz. There is also a home video on 1 videocassette (VHS) by the artist showing part of his home studio and some of the sculptures from his garden. Among the legal documents and certificates there is a folder with materials about Benton's law suit against Ed Marquand, an editor that was hired to work on a book about Benton's Kinetic Art between 1986 and 1987.
  - Photographs (Box 1)
    - Childhood Photographs, 1934-circa 1945 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Portraits of Benton, circa 1960-circa 1995 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      Oversized portrait moved to Box 9 folder 5
    - Family and Personal Photographs, 1962-circa 1990 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Benton with Art Personalities, 1975-1996 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Certificates, Awards, Diplomas & Certificates, 1981-2003 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Contract with Habenicht & Howlett, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Guggenheim Grant Application, 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Legal Records about Fletcher Benton's Book on Kinetic Art, Benton vs Ed Marquand, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Home Video: '3 Water Sculptures' (VHS), 1993; 1 Videocassettes (VHS) (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Caricature of Fletcher Benton and his Wife Bobbie Benton, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Biographical Texts about Benton, circa 1965-1975; 1974 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Includes two copies of the introduction used for the book Fletcher Benton: Selected Works 1964-74 by Diane Ghirardo Burke, De Saisset Art gallery
  - Unidentified Interview Transcripts, circa 1985 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Oversized portrait from Box 1, folder 2 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Correspondence, 1961-2014; Series 2; 1 Linear feet Box 1, 2 and OV 10
  The correspondence is arranged alphabetically by name and chronologically within each folder. Correspondence with less than three letters is filed in general alphabetical files. Letters with first names only, greeting cards and illegible signatures are filed at the end of the series. Additional correspondence can be found in Series 4, Exhibition and Commission Files. Some of the correspondents appear in Series 3, Interviews, and in the photographs in Series 1, Biographical Materials.
  Correspondence is with galleries and museums that exhibited Benton's work including the San Francico Museum of Modern Art, André Emmerich gallery, Gloria Luria Gallery, Howard Wise Gallery, Yares Gallery and Thomas Baebor Gallery. There is extended correspondence with curators George W. Neubert and Gerald Nordland as well as the British art critic and writer Edward Lucie-Smith.
  There is a series of correspondence related to Benton's exhibitions in Germany with the B. Haasner Gallerie and curators Jutta Brederhoff, Gerhard Kolberg, Peter Nestler and Jolie Leisegang. Leisegang was co-author of the book Fletcher Benton: An American Artist with Carter Ratcliff and Collette Chattopadhyay. There is also a large volume of correspondence with the prominent Dutch art collector Pieter Sanders and the Belgian contemporary art consultant Louise Descamps-Schneider.
  Significant personal correspondence is found with two of Benton's former professors from Miami University in Oxford, Ohio, Richard Clark Smith and the painter Edwin Fulwider. Personal correspondence also includes letters with the artists Pol Bury, George Rickey, Ulfert Wilke, Marlene Louchheim and the photographer David Finn. There are also two early letters from Benton to Lillian E. Jones, a mentor and arts' patron from Jackson, Ohio who supported the sculptor during his first years at New York City.
  - A, 1978-2011 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Aldrich Museum of Contemporary Art, 1969-1985 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - André Emmerich Gallery, 1989-2003 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Carol and Sheldon Appel, 1989-1997 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Leon A. Arkus, 1983-1986 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Arts Club of Chicago, 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - The Arts Commission of San Francisco, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Artists Equity Association, Inc., 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - B, 1980-2003 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Galerie B. Haasen, 1986-1988 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Joan N. Borinstein, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Jutta Brederhoff, 1987-2013 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Pol Bury, 1978-1994 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - C, 1983-2013 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Richard Clark Smith, 1979-1984 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Gisele Cottier, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - D, 1983-2011 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Louise Descamps-Schneider, 1992-2000 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Detroit Institute of Arts, 1984-1994 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - E, 1990-2013 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - F, 1982-2010 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - David Finn, 2001-2012 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Edwin Fulwider, 1978-1989 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Sidney M. Feldman, 1980-1985 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - G, 1985-2012 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Gloria Luria Gallery, 1983-1986 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - H, 1980-2010 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    Oversized drawing removed to OV 11
  - Howard Wise Gallery, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - I, 1977-2005 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - J, 1976-2013 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Lillian E. Jones, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - K, 1980-2013 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Paul J. Karlstrom, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - David M. Kezur, 1983-1987 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Gerhard Kolberg, 1993-1995 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - L, 1981-2013 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Jolei Leisegang, 1980-1987 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Tiziana Lorenzelli, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Los Angeles Art Center of Design, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Marlene Louchheim, 1980-2013 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Edward Lucie-Smith, 1989-1996 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - M, 1980-2012 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Metropolitan Dade County Florida, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Miami University, 1979-2011 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Muscatine Commission, 1980-1982 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - N, 1977-2013 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - George W. Neubert, 1983-1994 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Peter Nestler, 1989-1998 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Gerald Nordland, 1978-2010 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - O, 1986-2005 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Oakland Museum, 1967-1978 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - P, 1983-2012 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Pacific Mutual, 1980-1982 (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Barbara Pontecorvo, 2005-2006 (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Q, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - R, 1990-2010 (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - George Rickey, 1977-2005 (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - S, 1979-2014 (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - Pieter Sanders, 1981-1993 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - San Francisco Museum of Modern Art, 1981-2001 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - San José State University, 1977-1985 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Arthur Silverman, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Louis Skidmore Jr., 1978-1985 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Marvin Smalley, 1982-1991 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Herbert J. Solomon, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Sunset Magazine, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - T, 1985-2005 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Thomas Babeor Gallery, 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - U, 1974-1982 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - University of Arizona, 1980-1989 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - University of California, Los Angeles (UCLA), 1983-1993 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - V, 1980-2011 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - W, 1972-1994 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Frederick R. Weisman, 1986-1990 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Ulfert Wilke, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Yares Gallery, 1983-1985 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Yorkshire Sculpture Park, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Z, 2011 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - First Name Only, 1980-2013 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Greating Cards, 2010-2013 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Illegible Signatures, 1982-1996 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Oversized drawing from Box 1, folder 39 (Box OV 11)
- Interviews, 1977- circa 1990; Series 3; 0.3 Linear feet Box 2
  Interviews are arranged chronologically. Interviews from television and radio broadcasts are found in Series 6 Broadcast Materials.
  Series contains sound recorded interviews conducted by different journalists and researchers. Interviewers of note include those conducted by the British art critic Edward Lucie-Smith, Dan Tooker, Dan De Wilde, who interviewed Benton for a documentary on American sculptors. Interviews are on 1 sound tape reel and 7 sound cassettes.
  - Dan Tooker and Dan DeWilde Interview for Documentary "Contemporary Artists at Work, Sculptors", 1977; 1 sound tape reels Duration circa 45 minutes Handwritten note on original box: "Interview with Fletcher Benton by Dan Tooker and Dan DeWilde. August 1977. 7 1/2 ips, mono dub side one and side two (ca.45 minutes total) (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Katherine R. Alviso Interview, 1979; 1 Sound cassettes Cassette is a copy, location of original unkown; handwritten note on original cassette: "Conversation with Fletcher Benton. November 17, 1979 - interviewed at his studio in San Francisco, CA by Katherine R. Alviso. COPY" (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Susan Raeburn Interview, 1979; 1 Sound cassettes Duplicate; handwritten note inside the original box: " This is a duplicate of FB-RS Interview (transcribed)"; 1 Sound cassettes Original; handwritten note on original cassette: "Fletcher Benton-with Susan Raeburn. Competence + the modern Artist" (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Edward Lucie-Smith Interview, 1988; 1 Sound cassettes Handwritten note on original cassette: "Edward Lucie-Smith October, 1988" (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Bill Minschew Interview, undated; 1 Sound cassettes Includes two transcripts (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - George Neubert Interview, undated; 1 Sound cassettes Duplicate, location of orginal unknown; handwritten note on cassette: "Fletcher Benton Geo Nubert Interview watch copy" (Box 2, Folder 29)
- Exhibition and Commission Files, 1959-2002; Series 4; 1.9 Linear feet Box 2-4, OV 11-13, RD 14
  Arrangement is chronological. Additional information about exhibitions and commissions is found in series 2, Correspondence and series 5, Printed Materials.
  Materials include correspondence with galleries, museums and specific commission patrons; financial records; shipping and subcontracting documentation; audiovisual material and planning and design materials, including a significant amount of oversized materials. The most extensive documentation is found for the Folded Circle-Arc commission by Stanley Consultants, Inc. in Muscatine, Iowa; the California/International Arts Foundation Traveling Sculpture Exhibition; Double Folded Circle Ring in Brussels and Double Circle Folded by Cedars Sinai Medical Center in Los Angeles. Note that the folder of South American Materials contains correspondence, shipping records and inventories of artwork involving Estudio Actual (Caracas), Galeria Bonino Ltd, (New York) and Stanford University. An early exhibition in San Francisco is documented on motion picture film shot by Al Wong in 1967. Additional audiovisual material in the series include 2 videocassettes (VHS); one with documentation of the installation of Double Folded Circle Ring in Brussels, and a promotional video about Double Circle Folded in Los Angeles; and one sound cassette recording of the reception for Folded Circle-Arc in Muscatine, Iowa.
  - Gump Gallery, San Francisco, California (1960), 1959-1960 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Film Footage by Al Wong, San Francisco Art Institute Exhibition (1967), 1 Film reels Ektachrome Print 16 mm (Box 2, Folder 31)
    Film Reel removed to Box 9 Folder 1; Digital copy available on a DVD with two other films, copy filed in box 7, folder 6.
  - South American Materials, 1971-1976 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Art Club of Chicago (1979) (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Milwaukee Art Center (1980) (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Newport Harbor Art Museum (1980), 1980-1985 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Folded Circle -- Arc (1980), Muscatine, Iowa, Stanley Consultants, Inc. Commission (Box 2)
    - Correspondence and Documentation about the Commission, 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - Stanley Consultants, Inc. Dossier, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - Sound Recording of Reception for Fletcher Benton, 1980; 1 Sound cassettes Hadwritten note on the cassette: "reception for Fletcher Benton Stanley Consultants, Muscatine, IOWA Sept. 12, 1980" (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - Photographic Materials for a Public Exhibition, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Muscatine Art Center Exhibition (1980), 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Klingspor Museum, Offenbach, West Germany (1980), 1981 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Folded Square Alphabet 'D' (1981), Offenbach, Germany (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - "Polychrome," Hansen Fuller Goldeen Gallery, San Francisco, California (1981), 1981-1984 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - San José Museum of Art (1982), 1981-1985 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - "Brook House Sculpture Invitational," Kaiser Center, Oakland, California (1982), 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - California International Arts Foundation Traveling Sculpture Exhibition (1986), 1981-1986 (Box 2, Folder 46-47)
    Folder 47 contains copies of plans and drawings; oversized material moved to Box 9, folder 4
  - Fresno Art Center (1985), 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Gloria Luria Gallery, Miami, Florida (1984) (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Chapman College Sculpture Acquisition Program, Orange, California (1985), 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - "Teachers and their Pupils,'" Anna Gardner Gallery, Stinson Beach, California (1985) (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Artists Forum, Fine Arts Gallery, California State University, Los Angeles (1985) (Box 3, Folder 5)
    Oversized drawings moved to OV.11
  - Art Insitute of Southern California, Exhibition and Lecture (1986) (Box 3)
    - Correspondence and Documentation, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Photographs, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Thomas Babeor Gallery Exhibition, La Jolla, California (1986) (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Branson School Exhibition, Ross, California (1986) (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Folded Square Alphabet Q 10' (1986) IBM Commission (Box 3, Folder 10)
    Other Finding Aids note
    Oversized materials moved to OV 11
  - San Francisco Landscape Garden Show, Fort Mason Center (1986) (Box 3, Folder 11)
    Oversized materials moved to RD 14
  - "Furniture in the Aluminum Vein," Kaiser Center, Oakland, California (1986) (Box 3, Folder 12)
    Oversized drawings moved to Box 9, Folder 4
  - "Seven Artists in Depth: The Creative Process," San Francisco Museum of Modern Art (1986) (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - San Francisco Arts Commission Festival, Civic Center Plaza (1986) (Box 3, Folder 14)
    Oversized materials moved to OV. 11
  - Loan of Balanced, Unbalanced Wheels, City of Phoenix, Arizona, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Transamerica Redwood Park, San Francisco, California (1986) (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Art Store Gallery Exhibition, San Francisco, California (1987), 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - "Arts Irvine" (1987) (Box 3, Folder 18)